* NTSC (USA)
        
        * PAL (Europe)
        
        * Japan

        * NTSC (USA)
        
        * PAL (Europe)

        * NTSC (USA)
        
        * PAL (Europe)
        
        * Japan

        * NTSC (USA)
        
        * PAL (Europe)
        
        * Japan

        * NTSC (USA)
        
        * PAL (Europe)
        
        * Japan

NEW: [Funko Pop Figures](https://www.pricecharting.com/category/funko-pops)

Search  Prices Collection Market 

Privacy Policy
==============

We value your privacy and as web users ourselves know that you want the least invasive user experience possible. We collect, use, and share the least amount of information possible for our website services to operate.

This side is the actual privacy policy. It is legally binding.

This side is a summary. It is not legally binding.

### Data We Collect From You

We collect your personal information when you submit it to us via a webform or send us an email.

We also collect personal transaction information when you are logged into your account and use services on our site, make purchases, or sell items in our marketplace.

### Summary,

If you give us your personal info we will have it. If you have an account we will keep track of what you buy and sell on the website.

### How We Use Your Personal Information

We use your personal information to contact you about your account and transactions you make on the site.

We may provide your personal information to service providers to facilitate services on the site including but not limited to email delivery and payment processing.

We may use your personal email, wishlist, and account information to send you emails about items you are interested in. Some of these emails may contain affiliate marketing links.

You can opt-out of any emails we send with a one-click "unsubscribe" link in every email or changing your email settings in your account.

### Summary,

We will only use your personal information to contact you about your account and items that might be interesting to you. You can always opt-out of emails.

### Sharing Data with Third Parties

When you enter into a transaction on our marketplace, you give us permission to share your personal information with the other party to the transaction. We will only share information needed for order fulfilment. We will never share payment information, passwords, or phone numbers.

We do not sell, rent, or give away any of your personal information to any other third parties.

We will only share your personal and transaction information with law enforcement personnel when presented with a valid court order.

### Summary,

We share your information with people on the marketplace only when needed to complete a transaction. We don't share it with anyone else unless the law requires it.

### Information Retention

We retain personal and transaction information indefinitely. You can request us to remove your personal information. To preserve integrity of our database, we do not remove transaction informaton. If required by law, we will erase account information. You agree that all information submitted to us is the property of PriceCharting and can be used by us in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Summary,

We can keep and use your information until you ask us to remove it.

### Our Cookies

When you visit PriceCharting we might sent cookies to your computer. We use this information to remember user preferences, logged in status, and for some website features.

Some third party services deliver cookies as well. We use these to know traffic numbers and what features customers use.

At any time you can block cookies in your browser. Some features will not work correctly with our cookies turned off. There are no negative consequences to disabling third party cookies.

### Summary,

We use some cookies for website features like logging in. Some features won't work if you block our cookies.

### Advertising Cookies

This site uses cookies and similar tracking technologies such as the Common ID cookie for measuring advertising effectiveness and ensuring a robust online advertising industry. The Common ID cookie stores a unique user id in the first party domain and is accessible to our ad partners. This simple ID that can be utilized to improve user matching, especially for delivering ads to iOS and MacOS browsers. Users can opt out of the Common ID tracking cookie by clicking [here](#opt-out)

FOR EU USERS ONLY: When you use our site, pre-selected companies may access and use certain information on your device and about your interests to serve ads or personalized content. You may revisit or change consent-choices at any time by clicking [here](#cmp).

### Summary,

If you don't have an account, you will see ads on the site. Those users will have cookies placed on their device to improve ad effectiveness. You can opt-out.

* Categories

* Tools

* Navigation

* Other Links

* Policies

PriceCharting © 2007-2024  
We are user supported. We may earn an affiliate commission if you buy stuff after clicking links on our site to eBay or Amazon  

* USD |
    * USD
    * CAD
    * AUD
    * BRL
    * CNY
    * EUR
    * GBP
    * JPY
    * MXN
    * NZD

    * Dark 

[Login](https://www.pricecharting.com/login?return=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.pricecharting.com%2Fpage%2Fprivacy-policy) Don't Want Ads?

↶ ↷ ✓

Take/Upload a **Pokemon/Magic Card or Comic** photo. Find the best match in our database

Category Pokemon Card Magic Card Comic Book YuGiOh Card  

Take/Upload Photo  

Best Matches
